

ABOUT ME

Web Developer with 7 years of experience and has a strong background in front-end development. My expertise lies in developing web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks like Vue + NuxtJS and React + NextJS / Remix.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science AMA Computer College 2015 - 2018

SKILLS

HTML & CSS TailwindCSS

JavaScript Quasar

React AWS

Vue CICD

NextJS Bootstrap

Remix MySQL

NuxtJS Shopify

Graphal Pack Digital

LANGUAGE

English

Filipino

REFERENCE

Available upon request

DOMINIC RAFER

Senior Front-end Developer

+63 945 172 3257

raferdominic@gmail.com

😯 Cabuyao, Laguna, Phillipines

EXPERIENCE

Q Senior Front-end Developer

2024 - Present

Booth & Partners | Taguig

- Works alongside UX Designers and other cross functional team members to **implement website visions and designs to working code**.
- Front-end application maintenance such as package and content updates.
- **Implemented an observability platform** to their front-end application to monitor web performance and to track errors.
- Develops custom application for internal use on Shopify
- Collaborates with backend developers for front-end API integrations

Cloud Developer II

2021 - 2024

eCloudvalley Digital Technology | Taguig

- **Set the standards for front-end development** as a Cloud Developer that specializes in front-end development in the team.
- Handled the translation of UI/UX design into front-end development and the API integrations with the backend developers of the team.
- Built a **Front-end boilerplate** using **Vue + Nuxt + TailwindCSS + Quasar** to kick-start the frontend setup activities of the projects.
- Successfully delivered more than 10 projects including the internal projects of the company utilizing the boilerplate built.
- Consistently entrusted with multiple concurrent projects due to recognized expertise in frontend development.

Web Developer

2019 - 2021

Ximex Delivery Express Inc | Alabang

- Developed and maintained company IT systems
- Enhanced the Rubix Track and Trace platform with React.js and Ant Design
- Built new applications like the Express Box warehouse system and Payslip Automation tool using React, Laravel, and Lumen
- Contributed to server management and migration efforts.

Web Developer

2018 - 2019

Appsilog Inc. | Alabang

- Developed APIs for mobile applications using PHP.
- Maintained and updated client systems using PHP Codelgniter (backend) and Vue.js (frontend).
- Managed client requests and resolved system issues efficiently.